Guide to the Ira L. Wiggins Papers SC0177
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- General Files
  - Vanderbilt (George) Foundation (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Vermiliion Sea Expedition (San Diego Natural History Museum), 1962 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Vickery, Robert, 1952-64 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Wa - We correspondence, 1959-75 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Wh - Wi correspondence, 1960-72 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Wo - Wu correspondence, 1960-75 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Wagner, Warren H., 1964-71 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Walters, S. M. (Cambridge, Eng.) (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Ward, Daniel, 1964-68 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Ward, George, 1969-68 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Waters, Margaret, 1958-60 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Weber, William A., 1960-75 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Western Museums Conference (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Western Society of Naturalists, 1959-73 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Wheeler, L. C., 1947-49 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Wiens, Delbert, 1967-70 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Wiggins, "Additional Specimen of Pinus Pieperi.. .", 1950 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Wiggins, "The Development of the Desert Communities,", circa 1938 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Wiggins, "Effect of Prolonged Drought on the Vegetation in Southern Baja California" (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Wiggins, "Evolution of the Gymnosperms" (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Wiggins, "Observations on the Viscaino Desert and its Biota" (co-authors Alan R. Leviton and Allyn G. Smith), post 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Wiggins, "Seeds and Seedlings of Opuntia echios,". Cactus and Succulent Journal, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Wiggins, "Some Notes on the genus Galvezia", 1948 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Wiggins, "Systematic Botany in the U.S. and Mexico,", circa 1963 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Wiggins, biographical information sheet, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Wiggins, description (in Latin) of Peruvocereus Clavatus (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Wiggins, Malvacene for Flora of Sonoran Desert, preliminary drafts of (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Wiggins, observations on plants of Sonoran desert, pre 1950 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Williams, Louis O., 1964-69 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Williams, Maxcine, 1962-71 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Wolf, Carl B., biography (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Wolf, Carl B., biography (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Wolf, Carl B., biography (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Woodward, Carol H., 1948-49, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Y correspondence, 1947-70 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Z correspondence, 1947-1981 (Box 16, Folder 24)